Trust no one
Border Run is a thriller, crime film directed by Gabriela Tagliavini.
A female American reporter searches for her missing brother against the backdrop
of violence and human smuggling across the US/Mexican border.
Sofie, played by Sharon Stone.
Aaron, played by Billy Zane.
Rafael, played by Rosemberg Salgado.
Javier, played by Miguel Rodarte.
Juanita, played by Giovanna Zacarías.
Maria, played by Olga Segura-Gall.
Border Run (earlier title The Mule) is a 2012 American mystery thriller film
produced by Lucas Jarach and directed by Gabriela Tagliavini.
The film is based on true events and was released on DVD in February 2013.
Sharon Stone stars as an American reporter who searches for her missing brother.
The film depicts human smuggling across the United States/Mexican border.
The story is based on actual events.
The film explores themes of illegal immigration,
usa–mexico border, woman director.
The tone is intense.